<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<data>
	<item>
		<title>Sparkles</title>
		<link>http://www.flashxml.net</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2010 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<image>assets/Sparkles.jpg</image>
		<description><![CDATA[ <br> &nbsp; &nbsp; Sparkles is the founder and supreme high magical fairy of Syntax Ciphers.  He is a being that is primarily made up of sparkles and farts. He literally shits rainbows. He held the position of the fat jester of lollipop sparkle land and eventually accended to the position of fairy king. The rigors of leading the fairies and being in the midst of a sex scandal involving former members of the lollipop guild, he decided to relinquish his position and run a group of elitist intelligent virgins called the Syntax Ciphers.]]></description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Ryan "El Mancha de Mierda" Todd</title>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2010 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<image>assets/Mexican Ryan.jpg</image>
		<description><![CDATA[   &nbsp; &nbsp; El Mancha de Mierda grew a poor migrant worker outside of the borders of Juarez, Mexico. He primarily made a minimal amount of pesos turning tricks down by the fishing docks on the coast, catering to men who smelled sweetly of aquatic entrails. He met La Polla Gorda one faithful evening after the local sardine convention. Together, they decided to make a group that benefited the whole of the gringo promise land.]]></description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>RyanApple Vade</title>
		<link>http://www.flashxml.net</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2010 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<image>assets/Apple Fanboy.jpg</image>
		<description><![CDATA[ <br> &nbsp; &nbsp; RyanApple is our resident Minecrat fanatic and supreme Apple fanboy. When he is not trying to improve his dark side skills, he provides useful articles and advice that benefit the whole of Syntax Ciphers. You should ask about his sweet Apple leotard, he certainly rocks it well. ]]></description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>KyKg</title>
		<link>http://www.flashxml.net</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2010 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<image>assets/Cyborg.jpg</image>
		<description><![CDATA[<br> &nbsp; &nbsp; KyKg is our first ever cyborg member and had a lifelong dream of finally fusing himself with technology. He dream was achieved in the fall semester when he melded himself with his prized desktop "Watson". Since then, he has been heading up our thinktank group and providing useful feedback and ideas that help build the overall strength of Syntax Ciphers.]]></description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Dr. Howard</title>
		<link>http://www.flashxml.net</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2010 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<image>assets/Deandre.jpg</image>
		<description><![CDATA[<br> &nbsp; &nbsp; While Deandre Howard, an electrical engineer and lineman, was repairing a power line, a freak lightning accident caused a mutagenic change that transformed him into a living electrical capacitor. His powers were initially weak, so he spent some time stealing electrical equipment from Stark Industries to charge himself. During this time, he was approached by Magneto, who considered him a potential recruit for his Brotherhood of Evil Mutants, claiming that Howard's power rivaled his own, but Howard refused. He then joined the Syntax Ciphers and brought his talents to their endeavors.]]></description>
	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rueben Schmitt</title>
		<link>http://www.flashxml.net</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2010 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<image>assets/Andrew Weed.jpg</image>
		<description><![CDATA[<br> &nbsp; &nbsp; Rueben grew up on the streets of Jamaica a poor boy. He spent his days fighting for food until one day he moved to the States and started his own Oregano dispensery. His Oregano is used in some of the best Italian dishes this side of South Compton. Between his exploits, he lends his culinary expertise to the Syntax Ciphers and we enjoy every dish.]]></description>
	</item>
	<item>
		<title>Uncle Josh</title>
		<link>http://www.flashxml.net</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2010 18:37:00 GMT</pubDate>
		<image>assets/Creeper Josh.jpg</image>
		<description><![CDATA[<br> &nbsp; &nbsp; A creeper is a person who does weird things, like stares at you while you sleep, or looks at you for hours through a window. usually a close friend or relative. you know right away if that person is a creeper or does creeper things. it is not hard to spot the creeper.]]></description>
	</item>

</data>
